ACTWU President Jacob Sheinkman Files 5619/004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund [1 of 3], 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund [2 of 3], 1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Amalgamated Cotton Garment and Allied Industries Fund [3 of 3], 1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Clothing Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Multiple Subfolders
- Negotiations, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Clothing Manufacturers Association, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Central America Trip, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- National Labor Committee: El Salvador, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- El Salvador, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Canada, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- American Jewish World Service, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- American Jewish World Service, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Amalgamated Staff Retirement Plan, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation, 1983-1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation Meeting, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  April 30, 1984
- Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation Executive Meeting, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  September 20, 1984
- Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  October 15, 1984
- Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation - Draper Lab, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- South Africa, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Zensen, 1977-1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Xerox, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Xerox Corporation [1 of 2], 1985 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Xerox Corporation [2 of 2], 1986 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- United Nations Association of the United States of America [1 of 4], 1985 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Board of Governors Meeting
- United Nations Association of the United States of America [2 of 4], 1986 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- United Nations Association of the United States of America [3 of 4], 1985 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- United Nations Association of the United States of America [4 of 4], 1986 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Union Label (Dave Dyson), 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Trade, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Contains "1985 Trade Enforcement Act" and "Lobbying for Trade Enforcement Act" Subfolders
- Robert Richter Productions, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Retirees, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Resumes, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Rapid American Corporation, 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Comptroller Ed Regan, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- President Reagan White House Cabinet, 1980-1983 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Asa Philip Randolph Institute, 1980-1984 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- R Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Publix, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  April 12, 1984
- Public Relations, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Public Education Association, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Presidential Campaign, 1982-1984 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Program Planners, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Postgraduate Center for Mental Health [1 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Postgraduate Center for Mental Health [2 of 2], 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Political Action Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Plant Closing, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Includes "Plant Closing Testimony" (May 4, 1983) Subfolder
- Phelps Stokes Fund, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  One Large Red Binder
- Phelps Stokes Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- George Perkel, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Per Capita, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Pensions, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Palm Beach, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Staff Relations, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- South Africa, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Solomon and Rosenbaum, George Solomons, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Social Services, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Shoe Workers Pension Plan, Louis Simon/Health Center, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Includes Louis Simon Scholarship Fund
- Shoe Pension, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Shirt, Cotton Garment and Pants, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Shearson/American Express Inc., 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- New York State Senior Citizens Council, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Securities and Exchange Commission, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- S Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Roundabout Theatre Company, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Michael Roberts, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Victor Riesel, 1982-1983 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Leadership/Advisory Committee Conference (John Hudson), 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Peter Lazes Associates, Incorporated, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Labor Research Association, 1985-1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Labor Day Parade, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Labor Advisory Committee, 1985-1988 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- L Miscellaneous, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Kwasha Lipton, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Martin Luther King Junior Federal Holiday Commission [1 of 5], 1986-1988 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Martin Luther King Junior Federal Holiday Commission [2 of 5], 1987 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Martin Luther King Junior Federal Holiday Commission [3 of 5], 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Martin Luther King Junior Federal Holiday Commission [4 of 5], 1988 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Martin Luther King Junior Federal Holiday Commission [5 of 5], 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Kamber Group, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- K Miscellaneous, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Lichtenberg, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Licensing, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Noel Amanda Levin Memorial Fund, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Levi-Strauss and Company, 1974-1984 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Levi-Strauss (Tyler, Texas), 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Letters to the Editor, Etc., 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Legislative and Political Action Department, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Legal Department, 1986-1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Social Services, 1980-1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Organizing Department, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- New York State American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Legal Department, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Kayser Roth Men's Apparel, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Kayser Roth Men's Apparel, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- The Kamber Group, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- United Housing Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- United Furniture Workers of America, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers: Conference in Llandudno, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  May 1983 Noted in Folder Title
- Bakery Confectionery and Tobacco Workers International Union, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Unions Other Than Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- National Union of Hosiery and Knitwear Workers, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Szold and Brandwen, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- George Solomons, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Per Capita Payments, 1982-1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Citizens Action Committee, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Central Labor Council, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Central America Trip, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Canadian American Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Canadian Labor Congress, 1981-1984 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Canada, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- C Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- New York State Business Venture Partnership, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Brookings Institute, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Brookfield, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- British North American Committee, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Brigadier Industries, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Brandeis University, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Botto House, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Botany, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Black/Jewish Coalition, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Bass Shoes, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Frank Barbaro, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- B Miscellaneous, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Avtex Fibers, Incorporated, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Auditing Department, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Atran Foundation Incorporated, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Articles, Letters to the Editor, Etc., 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Arrow, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Community Council Social Service reports/Articles, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Community Council Medicare Task Force, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Community Council of Greater New York Ad Hoc Committee on Social Security, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Community Council of Greater New York Committee of Fiscal/Social Consequences, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Community Council of Greater New York, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Clothing Managers Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Clothing Manufacturers Association, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Clothing Negotiations Working File, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1982-1984 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Coalition for Progressive NYS Taxation (Franz Leichter), 1984 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Coalition for New York, 1982-1983 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Columbia Seminar on Labor, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Commercial Rent Control, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Commission on United States and Central American Relations, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Community Council of Greater New York, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Southern Textile, 1980-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Saint Louis Joint Board, 1979-1983 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Kayser-Roth, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Midwest Region, Textile Regional Office, 1981-1991 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania Keystone, Philadelphia Joint Board, 1980-1984 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Quebec Joint Board, Quin-State Region Joint Board, 1981-1983 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Southern Textile, Roanoke Valley Joint Board, Rhode Island, 1980-1984 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- South Carolina Joint Board, 1981-1984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- North Jersey Joint Board, Pacific North West Joint Board, 1979-1984 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Southern New England, 1979-1984 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Industrial Areas Foundation, 1984 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Textile Workers Miscellaneous, Kansas City Joint Board, 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Indiana Kentucky Joint Board, Gloversville Joint Board, 1981-1984 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Textile Workers Pension Fund, Los Angeles Joint Board, 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Maine Joint Board, Mid South Joint board, 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Mid Atlantic Joint Board, 1980-1984 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Clothing Negotiations 1982 Insurance Committee (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Clothing Negotiations Pension Committee, 1982 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Clothing Negotiations [1 of 3], 1982 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Clothing Negotiations [2 of 3], 1982 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Clothing Negotiations [3 of 3], 1983 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Communication Planners, Incorporated Proposal for American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1981 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- AFSCME, United Automobile Workers, Communication Workers of America, 1981-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- District 65 UAW, Furniture Workers, ICEF, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- International Ladies Garment Workers Union, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, National Union of Hosiery and Knitwear, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Service Employees International Union, National Union of Tailors and Garment Workers, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Kissinger Report, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Licensing, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Tidewater Joint Board, Alan Tobias, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  No files on Alan Tobias Included
- Tours of Shops, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Twin City Joint Board, Western Carolinas Joint Board, 1980-1984 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Trade, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- U Miscellaneous, Unions Other than Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union: Employment Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Union Label, 1982-1984 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Lawyers Committee for International Human Rights, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Legislative and Political Ed Department, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Levi Strauss, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Labor Advisory Committee, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Labor Council for Latin American Advancement, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Labor-Industry Coalition for International Trade (LICIT), 1983 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Labor Unity, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Labor Policy Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Betty Lall, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Western Region Joint Board, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- JTR Budget, 1983 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- K Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Kamber Group, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Edward Kennedy, 1979-1983 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- L Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- San Antonio Joint Board, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Shirt, Leisurewear, Robe, Glove, and Rainwear Workers Joint Board, 1981-1984 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- South Jersey Joint Board, 1982-1984 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Southern Regional Joint Board, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Southwest Regional Joint Board, 1980-1984 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Western Ontario, 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Local 752, Local 783C, Local 786, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Local 887, Local 892, Local 920, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Local 989, Local 998, Local 1034, 1976-1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Local 1055, Local 1060, 1973-1979 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Local 1085, Local 1099, Local 1175, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Local 1374, Local 1386, Local 1414C, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Local 1426, Local 1445, Local 1470, 1977-1979 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Local 1483, Local 1495, Local 1604, 1976-1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Local 1669, Local 1712, Local 1734, Local 1855, 1977-1981 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Local 1859, Local 1888, Local 2052, 1977-1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Locker Associates, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Londontown, 1979-1985 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Luzerne Apparel Corporation, M - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Made in the United States of America, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Local 173, Local 178, 1974-1978 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Local 181, Local 185, 1974-1981 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Local 187, Local 188, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Local 195, Local 208, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Local 217, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Local 221, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Local 224T, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Local 226, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Local 235, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Local 237, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Local 281, 1978-1981 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Local 288, 1975-1981 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Local 303, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Local 324, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Local 338, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Local 340, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Local 340 A, 1981-1984 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Local 352, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Local 362, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Local 365, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Local 377, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Local 424, General Union, 1974-1983 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Local 459, Local 491, Local 508, 1973-1983 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Local 590, Local 611, Local 615, 1972-1982 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Local 630, Local 677, Local 687, Local 689, 1977-1984 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Local 694, Local 710, 1975-1984 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Local 4, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Local 8, Local 10, Local 550, Local 63, Local 71, 1973-1984 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Local 110, Local 115, Local 125, 1973-1976 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Local 126, Local 153, 1965-1983 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Local 158, Local 161, 1974-1982 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- Local 162, Local 165, 1972-1976 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Local 169, 1981-1984 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Nuclear Freeze Disarmament, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- O Miscellaneous, Office Management, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Opinion Poll, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Organizing Election Memo, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- National Planning Association, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Notre Dame, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- National Immigration Refugee and Citizenship Forum, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- National Industrial Policy, National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Defense Fund, National Trade Union Council, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Memos, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Walter Mondale, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- N Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- National Coordinating Committee for Multiemployer Plans, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- National Council of Churches, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1982-1984 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Mayoral Campaign, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- McGregor Corporation, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- George Meany Center, 1983-1984 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Membership Figures, 1982-1983 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Occupational Safety and Health Association Environmental Network, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Interwear Negotiations, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Oxford University, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- P Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Occupational Safety and Health Association, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  Includes Subfolder "Eric Furmin Trip to South Africa", "ORT", and "Strikes"
- Organizing Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  Includes subfolders "Organizing meeting" and "Organizing Meetings"
- John Hudson, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Histadrut, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Scott Hoyman Pending, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Sidney Hillman, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Lewis Hine, 1982-1983 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Headwear Division, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Health Centers, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Healthtex, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Hanes Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Peter D. Hart Research Associates Incorporated, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Hartmarx, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Hathaway, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Gloversville Tanners, 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Greif, 1982-1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Guillermo J. Grenier, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Art Gundersheim, 1981-1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- FITITVC, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board Future of the Union Committee, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board, 1983-1984 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Research Department, 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Research Department, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- New York State Business Venture Partnership, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Industrial Cooperation Council, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Industrial Department, 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Labor Unity, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Legislative and Political Education Department (Liz Smith), 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- John Hudson, 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Human Rights, 1982-1984 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Industrial Cooperation Council Meetings, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Central North Carolina, Central and South Jersey, Chicago Joint Board, 1980-1984 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Cincinnati Joint Board, Text Deep South Region, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Delaware Valley Joint Board, Garden Spot Joint Board, 1981-1982 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Glove City Joint Board, Granite State Joint Board, 1980-1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Greater Cornwall Joint Board, Greater Fall River, Greater NY Joint Board, 1979-1983 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Greater Northern Textile, Georgia Tennessee Alabama Joint Board, 1979-1984 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Hudson Valley Joint Board, 1980-1984 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation, 1981-1984 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Textiles General Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Buffalo Joint Board, 1980-1982 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Textile Division, Canadian, 1981-1984 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Textile Staff Retirement Plan, 1982-1983 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Bi County Joint Board, Central Alabama Joint Board Textiles, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- JP Stevens 1977 Campaign (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union Strike Fund, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Superior Surgical, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Szold and Brandwen, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- T Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Tahari, 1983-1984 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Target, Tailored Clothing Technology Corporation, 1980-1984 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Stevens, 1981-1984 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- JP Stevens, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- ITGLWF, 1983-1985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Israel Labour Party: Peres, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Labor in China, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- New York City Labor: Religion Coalition, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Lawyers Committee for International Human Rights, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Hebrew Immigrant Aid Society, 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Histadrut Dinner, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  Folder title dated "5/14/83"
- History of Amalgamated, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Immigration/Undocumented Workers, Simpson-Mazzoli Bill, 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Import Demonstration, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  Dated 4/10/85
- Institute on Religion and Democracy, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans, 1984-1986 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  Includes folder "Trustee Committee"
- Economic Policy Council: Productivity Panel, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Federation for American Immigration Reform, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Fulton Ferry, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Fund for Modern Courts, Incorporated, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Bruce Gyory, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Helsinki Final Act, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Democratic Platform Committee Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 19)
  No dated material
- Drexel Burnham Lambert, David Sand, 1983-1984 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Economic Policy Council: Family Policy Panel, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Economic Policy Council: Financial Panel, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Economic Policy Council: Global Repercussions of US Monetary and Fiscal Policy, 1984-1985 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Economic Policy Council: Immigration, 1981 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Economic Policy Council: Jobs Panel, 1985-1988 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- Xerox, 1985-1989 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  Includes "Xerox Negotiations"
- Xerox (ESOP), 1989 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Y Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Zensen, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Workers Defense League, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Work In America Institute, Incorporated, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Xerox Corporation, 1988-1989 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Xerox Corporation, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration: Pam Woywod, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Pennsylvania Milrite Council, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Phelps Dodge Campaign, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Postgraduate Central for Mental Health, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Public Relations, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Asa Philip Randolph Institute, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- The Charles H. Revson Fellows Program, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Michael Roberts: Union International Systems, Incorporated, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Rob Roy, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- State University of New York, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Walter Fritz Mondale, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Legal Defense Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- National Immigration, Refugee and Citizenship Forum, 1985-1987 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Nettleton Shoe, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- New York City Elections, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- National Textile Recruitment and Training Program, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Nuclear Explosions, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 25)